Guide to the Yale Athletics Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographic slides documenting Yale athletics, 1905-1995; Accession 2006-A-007
  - Men's Sports
    - Baseball, 1905-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Basketball, circa 1970 -1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Crew, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Football
      - 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1973-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Harvard, 100th Game, 1983 November 19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13-17)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Army, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - College Football Hall of Fame, 1995 April 18 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - no date (Box 5, Folder 25-26)
    - Hockey, 1979-1990 (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
    - Lacrosse, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Soccer (captions available), 1982-1989 (Box 6, Folder 30-31)
    - Track/Cross Country, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Women's Sports
    - Basketball, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Crew, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Field Hockey, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Golf, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Gymnastics, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Lacrosse, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Soccer, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Softball, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Squash, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Tennis, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Track/Cross Country, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Volleyball, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Various, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Men's and Women's Sports
    - Hockey, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Swimming, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Track/Cross-Country, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Various, 1975-1989 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Cheerleading, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Photographs documenting Yale athletics, 1865-1982; Accession 2006-A-010
  - Men's athletics
    - Baseball
      - 1882 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1883 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1884 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1885 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1886 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1887 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1888 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1889 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1890 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1891 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1892 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1893 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1895 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1896 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1897 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1898 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1899 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1900 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1901 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1902 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1903 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1905 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1906 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1907 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1908 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1909 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1910 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1911 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1912 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1916 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1917 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1918 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1919 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - no date (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Basketball
      - 1911 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bicycling
      - 1895 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Captains
      - 1922 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Crew
      - 1873 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1876 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1879 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1880 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1881 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1882 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1884 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1885 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1887 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1888 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1889 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1890 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1891 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1892 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1893 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1894 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1895 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - no date (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Fencing
      - 1926 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1930 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - no date (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Football
      - 1878 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1879 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1880 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1881 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1882 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1883 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1884 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1885 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 1886 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 1887 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 1888 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 1889 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 1890 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 1891 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - 1892 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - 1893 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - 1894 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - 1895 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - 1896 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1897 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1898 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1899 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1902 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1903 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1905 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 1906 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1907 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1909 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1910 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1911 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1912 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1913 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1914 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1915 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1916 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1917 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1919 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1921 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1929 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1932 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - circa 1940s (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - circa 1950s (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - no date (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - no date (Box 5, Folder 23-24)
    - Gymnastics (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - 1878 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1892 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1893 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1895 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1905 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1906 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1907 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1908 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1915 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 1919 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - no date (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Lacrosse
      - 1926 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1947 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1949 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1951 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1952 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1953 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1954 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1955 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1957 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1958 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1959 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1961 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1962 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1963 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1964 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1966 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Rugby
      - circa 1870s (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Soccer
      - circa 1950s (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Swimming
      - 1914 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1919 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - circa 1920s (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1923 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1927 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1932 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1933 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1935 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1944 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1945 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1946 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - 1948 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - 1949 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - circa 1950s (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - 1950 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - 1951 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - 1954 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - 1959 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - circa 1960s (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - no date (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
      - no date (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Team Managers
      - 1895 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Track
      - 1886 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - 1887 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - 1888 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - 1889 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - 1890 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - 1891 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - 1892 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - 1893 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - 1894 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - 1895 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - 1896 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - 1897 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - 1898 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - 1899 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - 1901 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - 1903 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - 1904 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1908 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1910 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1911 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1912 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1913 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1914 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1915 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1916 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1919 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1920 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1921 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1922 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1923 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1924 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1925 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1926 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1927 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1928 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1929 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - circa 1930s (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1930 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1931 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1932 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1935 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1936 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1937 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1939 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - circa 1940s (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1940 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1941 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - 1952 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - no date (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - no date (Box 8, Folder 44-45)
    - Wrestling
      - circa 1930s (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Women's athletics
    - Fencing
      - no date (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Field Hockey
      - 1973-74 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Squash
      - 1974 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Track
      - no date (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Other
    - Class leaders, 1909-1913 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Physical examination, circa 1913 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Sculpture exhibit, Payne Whitney Gymnasium, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified groups, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Unidentified individuals, undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Oversize
    - Baseball
      - Men
        - 1905 (Box 10)
        - 1910 (Box 10)
    - Basketball
      - Men
        - 1983 (Box 10)
        - No date (Box 10)
      - Women
        - No date (Box 10)
    - Crew
      - Men
        - 1890 (Box 10)
        - 1908 (Box 10)
        - 1910 (Box 10)
        - 1911 (Box 10)
        - 1924 (Box 10)
    - Fencing
      - Men
        - 1923 (Box 10)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 10)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 10)
        - No date (Box 10)
      - Women
        - 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Field Hockey
      - Women
        - No date (Box 10)
    - Football
      - Men
        - 1876 (Box 10)
        - 1900 (Box 10)
        - 1967 (Box 10)
        - 1968 (Box 10)
    - Gymnastics
      - Men
        - 1903 (Box 11)
    - Ice Hockey
      - Men
        - 1931 (Box 11)
        - No date (Box 11)
    - Rifle Team
      - Men
        - No date (Box 11)
    - Swimming
      - Men
        - 1903 (Box 11)
        - 1904 (Box 11)
        - 1910-1911 (Box 11)
        - 1912 (Box 11)
        - 1912-1913 (Box 11)
        - 1926 (Box 11)
        - 1942 (Box 11)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 11)
        - 1953 (Box 11)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 11)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 11)
        - 1963 (Box 11)
        - 1964 (Box 11)
        - 1965 (Box 11)
        - 1966 (Box 11)
        - 1967 (Box 11)
        - 1968 (Box 11)
        - 1969 (Box 11)
        - 1970 (Box 11)
        - 1971 (Box 11)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 11)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 12)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 12)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 12)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 12)
        - 1976 (Box 12)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 12)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 12)
        - No date (Box 12)
    - Tennis
      - Men
        - 1966 (Box 12)
    - Track
      - Men
        - 1929 (Box 12)
        - 1931 (Box 12)
        - No date (Box 12)
    - Water Polo
      - Men
        - 1926 (Box 12)
    - Wrestling
      - Men
        - 1925 (Box 12)
    - Various
      - No date (Box 12)
- Athletic-related photographs, 1952-1969; Accession 2011-A-007
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Jack Blake, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - John Boyon?, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ? Doyton, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yale Faculty Club of New York, Football, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football Jerseys, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football - offices, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gymnasium - Physical Education classes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Handsome Dan, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Harkness, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Delaney Kiphuth and family, 1954, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Players with parents, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Yale objects memorabilia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Jordan Olivar, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - John Skillman, 1959, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Yale trophy room, 1952 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified groups, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified men, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified women, Yale Fence, 1956 November (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ronald Wails, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Yale-Harvard coaches, 1939 March (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Yale-Princeton, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Current Illustrated News, miscellaneous issue photographs, 1913-1915; Accession 2006-A-141
  - Current Illustrated News, miscellaneous issue photos, 1913-1915 (Box 1)
- Photographic negatives documenting Yale athletics, 1887-1963; Accession 2006-A-254
  - Athletic Association Functions, 1947-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Trainers, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Awards/Memorials, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1952-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Basketball, 1947-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Captains and Coaches, 1923-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cheerleaders, 1956-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Crew, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Crew, 1939-1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cross Country, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fencing, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Football
    - 1925-1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1955 (Box 3, Folder 15 - 16)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1959 (Box 3, Folder 21 - 22)
    - 1960 (Box 4, Folder 23 - 24)
    - 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 1963 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - no date (Box 4, Folder 29 - 30)
  - Golf, 1952-1962 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hockey, 1948-1963 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Intercollegiate Football, 1955-1962 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Intercollegiate Wrestling and Boxing, 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Lacrosse, 1887-1963 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Polo, 1957-1962 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rifle Team, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Rugby, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Ski Team, 1957-1962 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Soccer, 1952-1962 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Squash, 1950-1962 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Swimming, 1948-1970 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Tennis, 1950-1962 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Track and Field, 1956-1962 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Varsity Night, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Wrestling, 1950-1962 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Yale Bowl, Crowds and Games, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Various athletes, teams, and administrators, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 7)
- Photographs documenting Yale athletics, 1885-2001; Accession 2006-A-257
  - Baseball
    - Men
      - 1885 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1886 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1888 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1890 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1892 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1893 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1898 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1904 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1910 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1911 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1912 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1918 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1920 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - no date (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Basketball
    - Men
      - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - no date (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Crew
    - Men
      - 1881 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1893 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1895 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1897 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - no date (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 1)
  - Fencing
    - no date (Box 1A, Folder 2)
  - Field Hockey
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 3)
  - Football
    - Men
      - 1883 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1887 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1888 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1889 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1890 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1891 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1892 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1894 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1895 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1897 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1898 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
      - 1899 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
      - 1900 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
      - 1901 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
      - 1902 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
      - 1934 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
      - 1953 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1960 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1962 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1965 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1967 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1968 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1971 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1972 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1976 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1977 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1980 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1981 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1997 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - 1999 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 7)
  - Golf
    - Men
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 8)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 9)
  - Gymnastics
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 10)
  - Ice Hockey
    - Men
      - 1975 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
      - 1996 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
      - 1998 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 11)
    - Women
      - 1978 (Box 1A, Folder 12)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 12)
  - Lacrosse
    - Men
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 13)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 14)
  - Soccer
    - Men
      - 1978 (Box 1A, Folder 15)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 15)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 16)
  - Softball
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 17)
  - Squash
    - Men
      - 1957 (Box 1A, Folder 18)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 18)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 19)
  - Swimming
    - Men
      - 1945 (Box 1A, Folder 20)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 20)
    - Men and Women
      - 1980 (Box 1A, Folder 21)
      - 1985 (Box 1A, Folder 21)
      - 1987 (Box 1A, Folder 21)
      - 1989 (Box 1A, Folder 21)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 21)
  - Tennis
    - Men
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 22)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 23)
  - Track and Cross Country
    - Men
      - circa 1890 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - 1893 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - 1894 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - 1924 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - 1933 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - 1934 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - 2001 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
      - no date (Box 1A, Folder 24)
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1B, Folder 1)
  - Volleyball
    - Women
      - no date (Box 1B, Folder 2)
  - Various
    - Gerald Ford and George Bush with president of national football foundation (autographed), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Walter Camp memorial gateway (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Christmas cards, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gary Fencik [in Bears uniform] (autographed) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Kerry Jenkins, assistant women's basketball coach, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ray Kiputh with Stan Musial (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ray Kiputh with Herbert Hoover? (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Push up record, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Silver cocktail set presented to Mal Stevens by 1931 football team, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Special Olympics, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Photographs documenting Yale athletics, 1880-1990s; Accession 2006-A-260
  - Baseball team, circa 1910s (Folder 1)
  - Basketball - Yale vs. UConn, circa 1990s (Folder 1)
  - Coaches, circa 1928 (Folder 1)
  - Crew
    - Freshman, 1880 (Box 2)
    - 8 man crew, 1902, 1904 (Box 2)
    - 1906 (Box 2)
    - 1908-1909 (Box 2)
    - 1910 (Box 2)
    - circa 1910s (Box 2)
    - 1916 Jun 9 (Box 2)
    - circa 1920s (Box 2)
  - Fencing
    - 1950s (Box 3)
    - Varsity fencing team, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Football
    - Yale - Harvard football game, 1902 November 22 (Folder 5)
    - Team, 1905 (Folder 4)
    - Team, 1907 (Folder 4)
    - Yale - Princeton football game, 1905 November 18 (Folder 5)
    - Harvard - Yale football game, 1907 (Box 3)
    - Football, 1908 (Box 3)
    - Yale - Harvard football game, 1910 (Folder 5)
    - Construction of Yale Bowl, 1913-1914 (Box 3)
    - Yale vs. Harvard - first game played in Yale Bowl, 1914 November 21 (Box 3)
    - Team, 1916 (Folder 4)
    - Yale - Harvard football game, 1916 (Box 3)
    - Football team photo in Yale Bowl, 1919 (Folder 5)
    - Football captain Malcom Aldrich on fence, 1921 (Folder 4)
    - Team, 1921 (Folder 4)
    - Football, 1923 (Box 3)
    - 1934 iron men (Box 3)
    - Football, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Yale - Harvard football game, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Yale - Harvard football game, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Football captain McCormack on fence, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1921 (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1951? (Box 3)
    - Football team in front of fence, 1953 (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1960s (Box 3)
    - Football player Kenneth Wolfe (1961) (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1905 (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1905 (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1916 (Box 3)
    - Football captain Malcom Aldrich on fence, 1921 (Box 3)
    - Yale Bowl [aerial view], 1960s (Box 3)
    - Yale Bowl [aerial view], 1960s (Box 3)
    - Yale Bowl [aerial view], 1960s (Folder 4)
    - Football team, 1921 (Box 3)
    - Football team, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Gymnastics
    - 1900s (Folder 1)
    - 1900s (Box 2)
    - 1904 (Box 2)
  - Lacrosse, 1980s (Folder 1)
  - Soccer
    - Freshman team, 1953 (Box 3)
    - Freshman team, 1953 (Box 3)
    - Varsity team, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Track/cross country, 1927 (Box 3)
- Football lantern slides, circa 1915; Accession 2008-A-065
  - 50 lantern slides, circa 1915 (Box 1–2)